weekendnotes.com 2019-03-22

# Privacy

**Privacy Policy**

On Topic Media promotes an environment that respect individual privacy rights and personal information. On Topic Media is committed to care in handling personal information. 

**Purpose Of The Policy**

On Topic Media takes its obligations under the Privacy Act seriously and would like to take all reasonable steps in order to comply with the Act and protect the privacy of the personal information that we hold. This policy sets out how we intend to do so. 

The Policy applies to anyone who provides us with their personal information. 

**Information Collection**

On Topic Media may collect personal information such as: 

Your name 

Title 

Address 

Phone number 

Email address 

This information will be used only in a fair and lawful manner and used only for the purposes for which it is collected and when you knowingly provide it. 

**Use Of Personal Information**

On Topic Media will not disclose personal information without prior written approval, unless required by law. 

**Security**

On Topic Media undertakes to take reasonable steps necessary to ensure that private information remains confidential, and is secure from any unauthorised access or disclosure. 

On Topic Media's security measures include: 

restricted access to computer systems and physical records 

confidentiality agreements 

secure filing, storage systems and offices for physical records 

requiring employees to use unique passwords to gain access to our systems 

employing firewalls and virus scanning tools to prevent unauthorised persons and viruses from entering our systems 

secure access to building facilities 

**Gaining Access To Personal Information**

An individual may view his or her personal information at any time (subject to the Act) and advise On Topic Media if they believe the information is incorrect. 

On Topic Media has the right to deny access to personal information if: 

access would have an unreasonable impact on the privacy of others 

the request is frivolous or vexatious 

proceedings for a legal dispute are in place 

the information relates to a sensitive decision making process 

**Why We Collect Personal Information**

We collect the information in order to provide a service to our readers and clients. 

On Topic Media requests its employees to be vigilant in regard to the following issues: 

don't give out others personal information without their prior consent eg home telephone numbers 

written permission will be required before your personal information is given to others
